

# Marta Moros Batlle

## **INTRO**

I'm a Software Engineer/Web Developer with nine years of experience working as a Full Stack Developer. So far, I've worked with technologies such as Drupal, Symfony (PHP Based), SCSS, Javascript, and relational databases. I'm currently interested in shifting my focus towards current Frontend Development technologies (React, Nextjs, Gatsby, ...).

I've worked on several projects, including: Intranets for small and medium sized companies, e-commerce implementations, online education platforms, marketing websites, and shopping mall websites.

## **APTITUDES**

My roles usually include requisite analysis, solution design, implementation and maintenance, always with users in mind. I'm not an expert in UX but I'm interested in learning more about it. I like to learn about new technologies and apply them in real life projects. Although I'm not a professional designer, I enjoy doing it on my personal projects.

### **EXPERIENCE**

## **Hiberus Tecnología, Zaragoza** — Senior Web Developer

SEPTEMBER 2016 - SEPTEMBER 2021

- **Note**: Projects included in the "Junior Web Developer" section continued on this period, especially the ones relative to the team's main client.
- Drupal 9 marketing sites for lead capture (remake of existing site with new design)
  - PHP, Drupal 9, SCSS, Webpack, jQuery, Composer, Bootstrap, dataLayer (GTM), custom API for lead reception.
- Drupal 8, Shopping mall website (CC Urbil), Migration, evolution and maintenance.
  - PHP, Drupal 8, SCSS, Webpack, jQuery, Composer, Bootstrap. Custom API for external use, and use of third party APIs for the mall club membership.
- Internal tools for the company (Reporting and flow control tools)
  - o PHP, Symfony 4, Bootstrap, SCSS, jQuery, MySQL/MariaDB
- Intranet for "Comunidad de Usuarios de Aguas de la Comarca de Níjar". Complete code review and refactoring, focusing on billing and accounting systems.
  - PHP, Symfony 3.4, Bootstrap, SCSS, jQuery, MySQL/MariaDB.
- Styles (CSS) for extra projects as collaboration with other departments. (Gobierno de Navarra, Alain Afflelou stores intranet).
- Online courses platform:
  - Public e-commerce (CS Express):
    - PHP, Drupal 7, Drupal Commerce, oAuth, Apache Solr (para el buscador), SCSS, Bootstrap, ¡Query.
  - o Participation in course platform administration and classroom implementation

## **Hiberus Tecnología, Zaragoza** — *Junior Web Developer*

**OCTOBER 2012 - AUGUST 2016** 

- Evolution and maintenance of an Intranet for the team's main client. Analysis, design and implementation of functionalities for an e-learning organization.
  - o Zend Framework, SCSS, Bootstrap, jQuery, MySQL/MariaDB
- Evolution and maintenance of the marketing websites for the same client (between 5 and 7 sites depending on their active focus): Maintenance and optimization, new marketing sites development, Lead capture systems, Marketing vendors integration and Google Tag Manager integration through dataLayer.
  - o PHP, Drupal 7, SCSS, Compass, Bootstrap, jQuery, MySQL/MariaDB
- Migration, evolution and maintenance of a shopping mall website (CC Urbil). Implementation of the first integrations with external services.
  - o PHP, Drupal 7, SCSS, jQuery, MySQL/MariaDB
- Corporate website for the team's main client "Campus SEAS".
  - o PHP, Drupal 7, Bootstrap, LESS, SVG Animations (Snap.svg), jQuery

## **Pariver S.A, Zaragoza** — *Junior Developer*

DECEMBER 2011 - JUNE 2012 (Computer Engineering Final Project)

• Analysis and development of firmware updates manager software, to use in experimental zoneless induction kitchens (BSH).

#### **EDUCATION**

## **Universidad de Zaragoza, Zaragoza** — Computer Engineering

2004-2012

## **Universitat Politècnica de Catalunya, Barcelona** — *Computer Engineering (SICUE)*

2010-2011 academic year. Computer Engineering. Spanish Exchange SICUE.

#### OTHER EDUCATION

- Free Code Camp: React, Redux y React + Redux (2021)
- UX Learn Curso online de **UX Learn** sobre Usabilidad y Experiencia de usuario (January February 2016)
- Calligraphy courses and monographics with Victor Kams (2015, 2017) and Bego Viñuela (2021).

## **LANGUAGES**

- Spanish, native language.
- English, spoken and written (professional proficiency level).
- Català, limited working proficiency.

#### PERSONAL PROJECTS

- <u>CaliLíneas</u> Generador de guías caligráficas (work in progress, Made with React)
  - Other code projects at my <u>GitHub</u>
- Wordpress Blogs (<u>personal</u> and <u>collaborative</u>)